meetsoci.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy | SOCi

##### Effective January 1, 2015

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) covers SOCI, Inc. and MeetSOCI.com (“SOCI”, “MeetSOCI.com”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) and describes the types of information we gather from people visiting MeetSOCI.com (the “Site”) and from individual users (“you” or “users”) interacting with the applications we provide, and how we use such information. We understand the importance of privacy and accordingly, treat all information received in a responsible manner. By accessing the Site or interacting with our applications, you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Site, our applications or our services. Each time you use the Site, applications or services, the current version of the Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, when you use the Site, applications or services, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version.

##### Types Of Information We Collect

SOCI may collect three types of information from users of our Site: “personal information” which is information that can be used to locate, contact, or determine your or your business’s specific identity (such as name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, etc.); “aggregate information” which is information about your or your business’s activities on the Site or in connection with the services that cannot be used to identify, locate, or contact you or your business (such as frequency of visits to the Site, data entered when using the Site, Site pages most frequently accessed, browser type, etc.); and “social content information” which is information relating to the performance of social media content that is imported into, added to or scheduled from our Site.

##### Collecting Your Personal Information

SOCI collects personal information that is voluntarily provided when a user on our Site signs up for a price quote, or for an account on our site, or adds a new project on behalf of its client or otherwise uses one or more of our services (hereinafter collectively referred to as “personal information”). Specifically, when a user signs up for an account, we may ask the user for their name, email address, business information, among other information, and when the user uses some of our services including completing some of our templates or adding new projects, they may give us certain information about their or their customers’ business including address, telephone numbers, and other information. SOCI may also collect and store information about a user’s or their customer’s social media fans or followers (herein referred to as a “fan”) when such fan interacts with the user’s or user’s customers’ content. Such information is co-owned by us and the user the fan information is subject to this Policy and the user’s applicable privacy policy. Such information may also be owned and/or governed by third-party sites (e.g., Facebook). We make no representation or warranty about the user’s privacy policies or those of third-party sites, so if you are submitting information to any such third-party through our services, you should review and understand that party’s privacy policy before providing your information to them and us.

##### Collecting Your Aggregate Information

Aggregate information is collected as a user visits our Site or interacts with our services even if the user does not enter any information. Generally, aggregate information is used in a collective manner, and no single party can be identified by that compiled information. MeetSOCI.com uses aggregate information to provide its services and remuneration, as well as to determine the use of our Site and to monitor, audit and analyze information pertaining to our business metrics.

##### Collecting Your Social Content Information

Social Content information is collected throughout the Site, including but not limited to the Content Center, Listening and Analytics modules. Ownership of this content is governed by the Site’s Terms of Service (the latest copy of which you can find at http://www.MeetSOCI.com/terms-of-service.). Generally, SOCI will not use such social content information except on an anonymous and typically aggregated basis, such that no single user or user’s customer can be identified by that information. MeetSOCI.com uses aggregate information to provide its services and to monitor, audit and analyze information pertaining to general business and social metrics.

##### Sharing, Selling and Trading of Your Personal Information with Third Parties

MeetSOCI.com on occasion, may share personal information with third party service providers as we deem necessary for the third party to fulfill their duties, such as fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, or other functions necessary to our business. These third party service providers are not authorized to retain, share, store or use the personal information for any purposes other than to provide the services for which they have been hired to provide. When personal information is submitted, the user agrees that we may use the personal information to make contact with the party. We do not sell, trade or otherwise share personal information with unrelated third parties for their own marketing purposes, however, we may market certain offers on behalf of third parties.

We use personal, aggregate information and social content information in an effort to improve our users’ experience on the Site and with the services, and to communicate with them about information that they request. We may also use this information to help us target specific services or offers to users, to help us develop and improve the Site and services, and to tailor our Site and services to the users’ interests.

##### Sharing, Selling and Trading Aggregate Information and Social Content Information Collected Online with Third Parties

We may disclose aggregate information and social content information to third parties. Aggregate Information may be disclosed to third parties for a variety of business reasons, including to advertisers to inform them of the usage habits or characteristics of the interested audience, and to potential investors so that they may better understand our user base, etc. Social content information may be disclosed to third parties and to other users for a variety of reasons, including to give them better insights into general trends and consumer response metrics. Neither aggregate information nor social content information will include any personal information and we will not disclose any personal information except as expressly stated elsewhere in this Policy.

##### Other Instances When We Share Your Information

In addition to the foregoing, MeetSOCI.com may elect to share or transfer your personal information to unrelated third parties: (i) to comply with a legal requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on MeetSOCI.com, (ii) to investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of MeetSOCI.com; (iv) when we believe it is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of MeetSOCI.com or other persons, or (v) as otherwise required or permitted by law.

##### Cookies

If you do not provide us any of your personal information, we are limited in the information we may collect from you. For example, we may be able to determine your IP address for the purposes of administering the Site and tracking Site usage. However, your IP address may vary each time you visit or it may remain the same depending on the type of Internet connection you are using or the location from which you access the Site. We may also collect information about the websites that directed you to the Site after you clicked on a text or banner link or an ad from another website, or the day and time you visited the Site and how long you spent on the Site. We aggregate such information to help us to compile reports as to trends and other behavior about users visiting our Site; however such information is anonymous and cannot be tied directly to you.

We may also use “cookies” and your personal information to enhance your experience on the Site and with the Services and to provide you with personalized offers. A cookie is a small data file placed on your computer’s hard drive that contains information that allows us to track your activity on the Site. The cookie itself does not contain any personal information; however, if you provide us any personal information the cookie may act as an identifier to tie your personal information to your IP address or computer. You may choose to delete cookies from your computer’s hard drive at anytime or to disable cookies on your computer. If you delete cookies that relate to the Site, we may not be able to identify you upon your return to the Site. Additionally, if you disable your computer’s cookies, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site or services that require that cookies be enabled. The Site’s cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites. Additionally, our cookies cannot be used as a virus, Trojan horse, worm, or any other malicious tool that could impair your use of your computer. Our cookies are used to help us better understand how you and other users use the Site so we can continue to provide a better, more personalized user experience on the Site. We also share website usage information about our Site with those interested in running targeted promotional campaigns on the Site. For this purpose, we and our advertisers track some of the pages that you visit on the Site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs).

##### Security Pertaining to Your Information

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to MeetSOCI.com employees, service providers and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. We use secure socket layer (“SSL”) technology to encrypt and protect the security of your personal information, including but not limited to your credit card number, when it is sent over the Internet. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##### Integrity of Your Data

MeetSOCI.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

##### Children and Privacy

Our Site are not directed to children and we will not request personally identifiable information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 18, unless we have obtained verifiable parental consent from a parent or legal guardian. If we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered with our Site, provided personal information, and MeetSOCI.com has not obtained prior verifiable consent from a parent or legal guardian, we will immediately remove the user’s personal information from our files.

##### Links to Other Websites

The Site may contain links to websites operated by other people or companies. Those websites may have their own privacy policy or no privacy policy at all. MeetSOCI.com does not have any responsibility for those websites, and we provide the links solely for the convenience of our visitors.

##### Business Transfers

In the event that MeetSOCI.com sells substantially all of its assets, or one of MeetSOCI.com’s business units is acquired, personal information, aggregate information and social content information will likely be one of the transferred assets.

##### Changes to this Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on our Site. Your continued use of the Site and/or services indicates your consent to our collection of and use of your personal and aggregate information under the then current Policy.

##### Corrections/Information Removal/Opt-Out

If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other personal information changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by contacting MeetSOCI.com Customer Service at contact at MeetSOCI dot com. If you prefer not to receive newsletters or other marketing e-mails from MeetSOCI.com, please let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any newsletter or marketing e-mail you receive. If you prefer not to receive marketing mail via the mail carrier, please let us know by contacting customer service at contact at MeetSOCI dot com. Please be sure to include in any e-mail your full name, e-mail address, and any message. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective.

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time at contact at MeetSOCI dot com.
